http://drclarkstore.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Customer ServicePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer | Privacy | Security
100% Safe Shopping GuaranteeWe guarantee that every order you make at DrClarkStore.com is 100% safe.How do I know if the shopping cart is secure?You can verify if you are on a secure website if the address bar (URL) has an "s" after the"http". A secure page starts with https://. Our checkout pages are all encrypted for the safety of your personal information.Secure ServerAll Online Transactions are being processed with Industry Leading Secure 128-bit industry-standard SSL encryption held by Comodo Secure. Dr. Clark Store, Inc., is insured by identity assurance warranty of $1,750,000 subject to the terms and conditions of the Relying Party Warranty.
Credit Card Fraud ProtectionAll major credit card companies protect cardholders against fraud.E-mail NewslettersWe send special offers and coupons to our newsletter subscribers. You can always unsubscribe. Your email address will never be sold or rented.CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the consumer's hard drive, which contains information about how the consumer used the web site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our consumers to enhance the experience on our site. Cookies are used to power the shopping cart functionality when ordering from our web site. Usage of a cookie is linked to personally identifiable information while on our site. By setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.Parental ConsentOur privacy policy prohibits us from accepting members under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 are free to explore our site, but if they wish to become members or make a purchase we require that they do so through their parents' account. If you have additional questions or concerns, e-mail Service@DrClarkStore.com to reach our customer service department.Third Party IntermediariesTo complete credit card transactions, DrClarkStore.com provides the following member information using secure communications to Wells Fargo Bank: name, billing address, credit card number, expiration date, and amount of transaction. DrClarkStore.com shares shipping information with intermediary shipping companies such as FedEx.Notification of ChangesIn the event that DrClarkStore.com should change its privacy practices or start using member information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, an email will be sent to our members notifying them of the change. Our members then have the opportunity to accept the changed policy or demand exemption from it.
- Friday | 8 AM - 3 PM
Newsletter
Connect With Us
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Further Info
About Us
All prices are in USD.
© 2020 Dr. Clark Store
Loading... Please wait...
×
×
